Hannah is excited to be going to college.
汉娜对于即将到来的 大学生活感到十分兴奋。
She couldn't wait to get out of her parents' house,
她迫不及待地想要离开父母，
to prove to them that she's an adult,
向他们证明自己已经是个大人了，
and to prove to her new friends that she belongs.
并且有了属于自己的朋友圈。
She heads to a campus party
在一个校园派对上，
where she sees a guy that she has a crush on.
她对一个男生一见钟情。
Let's call him Mike.
让我们称他为迈克。
The next day, Hannah wakes up with a pounding headache.
第二天，汉娜在剧烈的头痛中醒来。
She can only remember the night in flashes.
她对昨晚的记忆只剩下零星的碎片。
But what she does remember is
她只记得
throwing up in the hall outside Mike's room
在迈克房间外的走廊上呕吐，
and staring at the wall silently while he was inside her,
想起当迈克在她身体里时， 自己只能无声的盯着墙壁
wanting it to stop,
等待着一切快点结束，
then shakily stumbling home.
然后，她跌跌撞撞的回了家。
She doesn't feel good about what happened,
对于所发生的一切， 她并不觉得美好，
but she thinks, "Maybe this is just what sex in college is?"
但她心想：“或许，这就是 大学里的性体验吧？”
One in five women and one in 13 men will be sexually assaulted
五分之一的女性和 十三分之一的男性将会
at some point during their college career in the United States.
在美国大学生涯里的某一时刻 遭遇性侵。
Less than 10 percent will ever report their assault to their school
但他们中只有不超过 十分之一的人会向学校或者
or to the police.
警局报案。
And those who do, on average, wait 11 months to make the report.
而这些被性侵的报案人， 平均要等待11个月才会进行举报。
Hannah initially just feels like dealing with what happened on her own.
汉娜本打算自己处理 在她身上所发生的一切，
But when she sees Mike taking girls home from parties,
但每当她看到迈克 从派对上带着其他女孩回家时，
she's worried about them.
她非常担心那些女孩。
After graduation, Hannah learns
在毕业之后，汉娜才得知
that she was one of five women who Mike did the exact same thing to.
她是被迈克性侵的五个女孩之一。
And this is not an unlikely scenario
事实可能比这更糟，
because 90 percent of sexual assaults
因为百分之九十的性侵案件
are committed by repeat offenders.
都是由累犯犯下的。
But with such low reporting rates,
但由于极低的告发率，
it's fairly unlikely that even repeat perpetrators will be reported,
即使是累犯，都可能很难被告发，
much less anything happen if they are.
更不用说他们会受到惩罚了。
In fact, only six percent of assaults reported to the police
事实上，在那些向警方告发的 性侵案件中只有百分之六的
end with the assailant spending a single day in prison.
性侵者受到了（最多）被拘禁一天的处罚。
Meaning, there's a 99 percent chance that they'll get away with it.
这意味着，在美国他们将有 百分之九十九的可能逃之夭夭 。
This means there's practically no deterrent to assault
这说明在美国， 对于此类性侵案的实际震慑力
in the United States.
非常小。
Now, I'm an infectious disease epidemiologist by training.
我是一个受训的 主攻感染性疾病的流行病学家。
I'm interested in systems and networks
我对系统和网络十分感兴趣，
and where we can concentrate our resources to do the most good.
那是一个我们能聚集我们的研究成果 以达到最好效果的地方。
So this, to me, is a tragic but a solvable problem.
因此在我看来，性侵是一个 无比悲痛，但却是一个可以解决的问题。
So when the issue of campus assault started hitting the news a few years ago,
所以，当校园性侵事件 在几年前上了新闻头条时，
it felt like a unique opportunity to make a change.
我想，这会是一个独一无二的 做出改变的机会。
And so we did.
并且，我们做到了。
We started by talking to college survivors.
我们从采访校园性侵案的幸存者开始。
And what they wish they'd had in college is pretty simple;
这些人的愿望其实很简单；
they wanted a website,
他们希望有一个网站，
one they could use at the time and place
能够让他们在自己觉得安全的
that felt safest to them
时间和地点使用，
with clearly written information about their reporting options,
具有可供选择的举报方式，
with the ability to electronically report their assault,
以及自动生成案件举报报告的功能，
rather than having the first step
而不是在一开始就需要
to go in and talk to someone who may or may not believe them.
在一个房间中， 向一个不确定是否会相信他们的人诉说。
With the option to create a secure, timestamped document
网站还应具有一个安全的， 有时间标记的文件档案
of what happened to them,
记录整个性侵事件的经过，
preserving evidence even if they don't want to report yet.
保存下证据，即使 受侵害者暂时还不想告发。
And lastly, and perhaps most critically,
最后，同时可能也是最关键的一点，
with the ability to report their assault
当有其他人告发了相同的性侵者时，
only if someone else reported the same assailant.
网站就会报道出受害者的遭遇。
You see, knowing that you weren't the only one changes everything.
你瞧，你不是惟一一个 去改变一切的人。
It changes the way you frame your own experience,
这个网站改变了你 对待自己所经历的事的方式，
it changes the way you think about your perpetrator,
它改变了你看待作恶者的角度，
it means that if you do come forward,
它意味着如果你向前进一步，
you'll have someone else's back and they'll have yours.
你将会得到其他人的支持， 她们也同样会得到你的支持。
We created a website that actually does this
我们创造了一个可以将这些实现的网站，
and we launched it [...] in August,
并且我们在两个月前开始运作， 在今年8月份在两所大学中
on two college campuses.
开始使用。
And we included a unique matching system
我们打造了一个独特的匹配系统，
where if Mike's first victim had come forward,
当遭受迈克性侵的第一位受害者报过案后，
saved her record, entered into the matching system
网站会将她的记录保存 并放入匹配系统中，
and named Mike,
将其命名为迈克。
and Mike's second victim had done the same thing
几个月后，当遭受迈克性侵 的第二位受害者
a few months later,
在系统中记录下案件时，
they would have matched
两起案件会自动匹配，
and the verified contact information of both survivors
案件幸存者的联系方式
would have been sent to the authorities at the same time
经核实后同时被送往当局
for investigation and follow up.
以供调查和实时追踪。
If a system like this had existed for Hannah and her peers,
如果有一个这样为汉娜 和她的同伴所打造的系统，
it's more likely that they would have reported,
这个系统让她们能更加主动的告发案件，
that they would have been believed,
更容易被他人相信，
and that Mike would have been kicked off campus,
而这样，迈克将更有可能被退学，
gone to jail, or at least gotten the help that he needed.
送往监狱，或者至少 得到他所需要的帮助。
And if we were able to stop repeat offenders like Mike
如果我们能在诸如迈克一样的 累犯在第二次性侵事件
after just their second assault following a match,
被系统匹配后，立刻制止他，
survivors like Hannah would never even be assaulted
像汉娜一样的幸存者就将避免
in the first place.
受到侵害。
We could prevent 59 percent of sexual assaults
我们通过及早制止屡次作案的罪犯，
just by stopping repeat perpetrators earlier on.
可以防止百分之五十九的性侵案件发生。
And because we're creating a real deterrent to assault,
我们正建立一个真正的 对性侵案件具有威慑力的系统，
for perhaps the first time,
因此在第一时间，
maybe the Mikes of the world would never even try to assault anyone.
世界上的“迈克们” 将可能永远没有机会去性侵他人。
The type of system I'm describing,
这个我正在向您介绍的系统，
the type of system that survivors want
同时也是那些幸存者所期盼的系统，
is a type of information escrow,
是一类信息契约，
meaning an entity that holds on to information for you
这种契约为你保存你的信息，
and only releases it to a third party
并在条件达到某些协议约定的时候，
when certain pre-agreed upon conditions are met,
才向第三方透露你的信息，
such as a match.
例如一次匹配。
The application that we built is for college campuses.
这是我们为大学所打造的系统。
But the same type of system could be used in the military
同样类型的系统也可应用于军队中，
or even the workplace.
或者工作场所。
We don't have to live in a world
我们不是一定要活在
where 99 percent of rapists get away with it.
百分之九十九的性侵者都会逃脱的世界。
We can create one
我们有能力创造一个世界，
where those who do wrong are held accountable,
在那里，违者必究，
where survivors get the support and justice they deserve,
在那里，幸存者能得到 她们应得的支持和正义，
where the authorities get the information they need,
在那里，当权者能得到他们所需的信息，
and where there's a real deterrent
那里对于侵犯他人权利的人
to violating the rights of another human being.
会具有真正的威慑力。
Thank you.
谢谢。
(Applause)
（掌声）